

# MARKEL ZUBIZARRETA

UX/UI DESIGNER

markelzubi@gmail.com

Portfolio  $\rightarrow$ 

# **PROFILE**

As a UX/UI Designer, my expertise lies in crafting **digital experiences** by understanding **user needs**.

With a strong background in graphic design and digital marketing, I transform these insights into innovative and visually appealing interfaces that drive tangible results.

# SKILLS

I have experience on engaging in brainstorming sessions, whiteboarding concepts, creating sitemaps, userflows and wireframes at different levels of fidelity. Software that I'm familliar with:

- Figma
- Sketch
- · Adobe Creative Suit
- HTML & CSS
- Webflow
- Framer
- Notion

## **PROJECTS**

### PI ANIFY

App to discover and organize trip plans

- UX research, surveys/interviews, wireframeing, sitemap and userflow.
- UI design, branding, foundation, design system and high fidelity prototype.

#### **SAVER**

Personal finance management app

- UX research, surveys/interviews, wireframeing, sitemap and userflow.
- UI design, branding, foundation, design system and high fidelity prototype.

### **PIENSO EXPRESS**

eCommerce web redesign of a pet store

- UX research, surveys/interviews, wireframeing, sitemap and userflow.
- UI design and high fidelity prototype.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## Diggia Group

2020 - Now

Digial Design Specialist

- UX design: conduct interviews/surveys, wireframeing, sitemaps and userflows.
- UI design: createing a design system, foundation and high fidelity prototypes.
- Branding and corporate design. Elaboration of brandbook and definition and delimitation of brand graphic elements.
- Graphic design for social media, banners and visuals for website and social ads.
- Design of documentation, presentations, catalogs and corporate magazine.
- · Design of merchandising, packaging, vinyls, stands, displays and rollups.

**MAPFRE** 2018 - 2019

Graphic Design Specialist

- · Graphic design for social media creativities and visuals for website.
- Design infographics and graphic diagrams for for web and documents.
- · Layout of magazines and quarterly reports. Presentations and photo editing.
- Web design using Wordpress and Elementor.

#### Federación Vizcaína de Golf

2017 - 2018

Graphic Design Intership

- · Design of web banners, business cards or brochures using Adobe Creartive Suit.
- Web design using Wordpress and Elementor.

# EDUCATION

### Ironhack Madrid

2023

UX/UI Design Bootcamp

- · Multiple projects, both individually and collaboratively.
- Design of various digital products, including websites and apps.
- Surveys/interviews, brainstorming, wireframeing, sitemaps and userflows.
- High fidelity interactive prototypes with animations and design systems.
- Foundational understanding of HTML5 and CSS3.
- Final project: Planify, app to discover and organize trip plans.
  - Chosen as Top Project of the promotion at Hackshow event.

## **EAE Business School**

2019 - 2020

Digital Marketing and eCommerce Master's Degree

- Minor in Neuromarketing: deepening my understanding in user centric design.
- Final project: Helper, design of a domestic services app.

## University of the Basque Country

2012 - 2016

Advertising and PR Bachelor's Degree

- Minor in Digital Design: focused on developing design skills for digital media.
- · Final project: Art direction in environmental advertising.